{"data":[{"question":"The minister warned the whole nation ___ after drinking.","a":"to never drive","b":"never to drive","c":"never drive","d":"never driving","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Want sbd (not\/never) to do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The next morning the maid found her master ___ in bed, dead.","a":"lie","b":"lying","c":"laying","d":"lay","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The clerk scolded the girl caught ___ and called the police.","a":"to be stealing","b":"to have stolen","c":"stealing","d":"to steal","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Good morning. What may I do for you? \"I'd like to have this parcel ___, sir.\"","a":"to be weighed","b":"be weighed","c":"weighed","d":"to weigh","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice: Have\/has sth done","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The 2 murderers were brought in, with their hands ___ behind their backs.","a":"having tied","b":"being tied","c":"tied","d":"to be tied","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tied = were tied (passive voice, \"were\" is hidden)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"It is wise to have part of one's income ___ for old age.","a":"put away","b":"kept up","c":"given away","d":"laid up","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Passive voice: Have\/has sth done ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The managers discussed the proposal that they would like to see ___ the next month.","a":"carrying out","b":"carry out","c":"to carry out","d":"carried out","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Passive voice: - Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ PP ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm hungry. Is there anything ___.","a":"to eat","b":"eat","c":"for eating","d":"eating","answer":"1","explain":"\n- There's + something\/ anything \/ nothing....+ To Verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The purpose of new-developed technologies is to make life easier, ___ it more difficult.","a":"not to make","b":"not make","c":"do not make","d":"not making","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Be to Verb= imply the \"purpose\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The sofa looks quite hard, but in fact it is very comfortable to ___.","a":"sit on","b":"sit","c":"be sat on","d":"be sat","answer":"1","explain":"- Sit on the sofa","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}